4xp.com 2012-09-13

# Privacy Policy

## No matter if you are a former or an existing client or just a visitor on our website, the privacy of our users is one of Forex Place Ltd.'s main concerns, therefore Forex Place Ltd is committed to safeguard all personal information collected from our valued clients. 

By providing Forex Place Ltd with your personal information such as Full Name, Mailing Address, ID number, Passport Number etc., you are providing Forex Place Ltd with full consent to gather, utilize, store and protect the information provided in the manner described below. 

## **When is Information Collected from Forex Place Ltd.'s Clients:**

  * When opening a Live/Demo trading account with Forex Place Ltd. (When filling in electronic registration forms).
  * When funding your personal trading account.
  * When withdrawing from your personal trading account.

## **The Personal Information that may be Collected Includes:**

  * Personal Information such as Full Name, Address, Date of Birth, ID Number and Occupation
  * Financial Information such as assets, investment experience and monthly income, in order to evaluate your trading experience
  * When funding your account or withdrawing from your account, we may request documents such as a copy of an ID Document, Utility Bills and a Bank Statement The above information collected from clients, helps Forex Place Ltd. understand your financial needs, provide you with products and services suitable to your needs, process your account transactions in a timely manner as well as provide you with the highest level of customer support.

## **How is information collected from Forex Place Ltd. Clients**

Clients willingly provide Forex Place Ltd. with the personal information collected in the following ways:

  * On Completion of Electronic registration forms placed on the Forex Place Ltd Website or on a Forex Place Ltd Minisite.
  * When funding or withdrawing from trading accounts, clients voluntarily provide required documents
  * When trading on the Forex Place Ltd system
  * When contacting Forex Place Ltd or responding to a promotion advertised

There is certain information that is indirectly collected by Forex Place Ltd such as: IP Address, operating system, software configuration and the use of cookies. 

## **Use of "cookies" on Forex Place Ltd.**

Forex Ltd. reserves the right to use visitors' Web site usage information to target our Internet advertisements on this site and other sites. After a visit to the site, third party vendors, including Google may display Forex Place ads, and may use the client's cookies to promote ads based on any prior visit to Web site. However, users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. 

## **What is the use of information collected by Forex Place Ltd:**

Forex Place Ltd will utilize the information collected from clients for the following purposes:

  * To verify clients identity
  * To set up, maintain and manage clients' personal trading account
  * To process deposits and withdraws in clients' personal trading account
  * To keep clients up to date with news, updates and new promotions at Forex Place Ltd.
  * To analyze client activity in order to improve and provide clients with the best products and services
  * To provide clients with top quality customer support

## **The Sharing of Clients Personal Information:**

Forex Place Ltd does not share any client information with any affiliated or unaffiliated 3rd parties and only under the below circumstances will client's personal information be shared:

  * In order to open, operate and service your personal trading account, Forex Place Ltd. may share information with service providers such as attorneys, accountants, auditors, and other financial professionals
  * In order to protect against fraud, money laundering, unauthorized transactions, claims or other liabilities
  * Income, credit history, net worth, or income information, will not be shared by Forex Place Ltd. under no circumstances
  * The company may share information with affiliates and introducing brokers, mainly for the calculation of these entity's compensation

## **How do Forex Place Ltd. Protect the Information you Provide**

Right on top of the Forex Place Ltd. priority list is clients security, therefore Forex Place Ltd. take all the necessary steps to make sure that your data is safe with us.

  * Forex Place Ltd. use the top notch data security technology, firewalls and data encryption
  * Every client owns his own personal user name and password which he uses to access Forex Place Ltd. systems
  * All client information at Forex Place Ltd. is restricted to a small group of management and employers that need to use this information

## **Links found on the Forex Place Ltd. Website**

Links to external sites may be found on the Forex Place Ltd. website. Forex Place Ltd. take no responsibility for the content on the external websites and advise to all clients to read the privacy policy of the external websites before leaving any personal information. The Forex Place Ltd. Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Forex Place Ltd..

##  **Questions, Concerns or Complaints?**

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints, please don't hesitate to contact us via phone, email or chat 24/5. Forex Place Ltd. offers customer support in over 10 different languages.

**We wish you successful trading!**
